A Guide to the Agricultural Development Council records, Record Group 1 FA078
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General, 1953-1977; 1
  - General - Publications, 1.5
    - Books and Monographs (Box 5, Folder 28)
      Southworth, Herman and Milton Barnett (edits.) Experience in Farm Mechanization in South East Asia. Singapore. 1974.
    - Books and Monographs (Box 5, Folder 29)
      Stevenson, Russell. Graduate Study in the United States. An Introduction for the Prospective Council Fellow. NY. 1968 and 1975.
      Taylor, Donald C. Research On Agricultural Development in Selected Middle Eastern Countries. NY. 1968.
      Wharton, Clifton R., Jr. Research On Agriculture Development in Southeast Asia. NY. 1965 and 1968.
      Wharton, Clifton R., Jr. The Role of Farmer Education in Agricultural Growth. NY. 1964.
      The U.S. Graduate Training of Asian Agricultural Economists. NY. 1959.
    - Directory of Fellows, 1963-1976 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Newsletter, Nos. 1-36, 1957-1977 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Papers (A-P) (Box 5, Folder 32)
      No author. The Bangkok Conference. June 1970.
      Beers, Howard W. Application of Sociology in Development Programs. January 1963.
      Bradfield, Richard. Toward More and Better Food for the Filipino People and More Income for her Farmers. December 1966.
      Brown, David W. A General Framework for Decision-Making in Agriculture. n.d.
      Brown, David W. A Visit with Rajab bin Harun: A Malay Coconut Producer and Fisherman. March 1963.
      Castillo, Gelia T. Man with Many Faces: The Researcher in a Program of Planned Change. April 1964.
      Hrabovszky, J.P. and T.K. Moulik. Economic and Social Factors Associated with the Adoption of an Improved Implement: A Study of the Olpad Thresher in India. May 1967.
      Hsu, Yu-chu. A Case Study of a Farm at Ching-Shui, Taichung, Taiwan, The Republic of China, 1960. November 1962.
      Jodha, N.S. A Semi-Namadic Farm Family. December 1966.
      Kearl, Bryant E. What Should Be the Role of the Social Sciences in a College of Agriculture? May 1966.
      Lewis, A.B. Intensive Summer Course in Practical Methods of Agricultural Economics Research: A Recipe. November 1967.
      Lewis, A.B. Thoughts on the American Training of Graduate Students of Agricultural Economics from Less-Developed Countries. January 1959.
      Mellor, John W. Village-Level Research. May 1960.
      Mosher, A.T. The Role of Agricultural Economics in Agricultural Development. May 1960.
      Penny, David H. Case Study of a Farm in East Sumatra. March 1963.
      Penny, David H. The Ciawi Training Center. May 1973.
      Provinse, John H. Western Research Techniques and Non-Western Values. May 1960.
    - Papers (S-W) (Box 5, Folder 33)
      Sajogyo,. Summary of Agro-Economic Survey Activities from September, 1968 to October, 1969. November 1970.
      Sitton, Gordon R. Farm Management Research. January 1960.
      Sitton, Gordon R. The Relationship between Marketing and Farm Managment. March 1960.
      Sitton, Gordon R. The Role of the Farmer in the Economic Development of Thailand. September 1962.
      Takashashi, Iichiro. Principles of Farm Labor Input in Family Farms in the Kyushu District, Japan. June 1962.
      Wharton, Clifton R., Jr. Economic and Non-Economic Factors in the Agricultural Development of Southeast Asia: Some Research Priorities. June 1963.
    - Reprints (A-N) (Box 6, Folder 34)
      Adegboye, R.O. Procuring Loan Through Pledging of Cocoa Trees.
      Beers, Howard W. Motivation for Community Development.
      Beers, Howard W. Testing Old Rules for Suitability in New Flaces. Proposals for Adaptive Research.
      Bruner, Richard. The Puebla Project.
      Byrnes, Francis C. Some Missing Variables in Diffusion Research and Innovation Strategy.
      Fisk, E.K. Development Goals in Rural Melanesia.
      Haq, Mahbub ul. Perspective on Development.
      Hsieh, S.C. Management Decisions on Small Farms in Taiwan.
      Iglesia, Jesus C. Sta. Review of Farm Management Work in the Philippines.
      Khan, Akhter Hameed. A History of the Food Problem.
      Ladejinsky, Wolf. The Green Revolution in Bihar - The Kosi Area: A Field Trip. The Green Revolution in Punjab: A Field Trip.
      Lele, Uma J. and John W. Mellor. Jobs, Poverty and the "Green Revolution".
      Mellikan, Max F. Education for Innovation.
      Mosher, Arthur T. Education, Research and Extension in Agricultural Economics in Asia and Latin America Today.
      Mosher, A.T. Learning to Think about Farming.
      Mosher, A.T. Projects of Integrated Rural Development.
      Nerlove, Marc. Economic Growth and Population: Perspectives of the "New Home Economics".
      Niehoff, Arthur H. and J. Charnel Anderson. The Process of Cross-Cultural Innovation.
    - Reprints (P-W) (Box 6, Folder 35)
      Penny, David H. The Ciawi Training Center. A Case Study in the Teaching of Social Science Research Methods.
      Rostow, Walt W. Agriculture's Role in Economic Development.
      Schickele, Rainer. Farm Management Research for Planning Agricultural Development.
      Schuh, G. Edward. The New Macroeconomics of Agriculture; and Warley, T. K. Agriculture in International Economic Relations.
      Seers, Dudley. The Meaning of Development.
      Silk, Leonard. Wanted: A More Human, Less Dismal Science.
      Streeten, Paul P. Social Science Research on Development: Some Problems in the Use and Transfer of an Intellectual Technology.
      Wharton, C.R., Jr. Economic Meaning of Subsistence.
      Wharton, Clifton R., Jr. Malayan Rubber Supply Conditions.
      Wharton, C.R., Jr. Marketing, Merchandising and Moneylending: A Note on Middleman Monopsony in Malaya.
    - Researcher, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Staff Papers, 73-1 - 75-2 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Staff Papers, 75-3 - 76-5 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Survey Research Methodology Papers (C-N) (Box 6, Folder 39)
      Castillo, Gelia. Research and the Action Programs. December 1972.
      Chaudhari, Haider Ali. Preparing Research Proposals. 1972.
      Nasoetion, Andi Hakim. An Introduction to Some Tests of Significance.
      Nasoetion, Andi Hakim. Some Statistical Principles and Procedures.
      Nasoetion, Andi Hakim. Some Statistical Properties of Samples.
    - Survey Research Methodology Papers (P-S) (Box 6, Folder 40)
      Parel, Christina P. and Gloria C. Caldito, Pilar L. Ferrer, Generoso G. de Guzman, Ceferino S. Sinsioco, Rudy H. Tan. Sampling Design and Procedures. 1973.
      Shah, Vimal. Reporting Research. December 1972.
      Shah, Vimal. Reporting Research. 1977.
    - Survey Research Methodology Papers (S-T) (Box 7, Folder 41)
      Shah, Vimal. Research Designs and Strategies. December 1972.
      Taylor, Donald C. Using Sorting Strips to Process and Analyze Data. December 1973.
    - Teaching Forum, Nos. 1-32, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Teaching Forum, Nos. 33-47, 1973-1976 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Teaching and Research Forum, Nos. 1-5, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Miscellaneous Bound Volumes - XV - Annual Reports - Directory of Fellows (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Miscellaneous Bound Volumes - XVI - Research and Training Network (RTN) Workshops - Reprints, Seminar Reports, Newsletters (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Miscellaneous Bound Volumes - XVII - Staff Papers (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Miscellaneous Bound Volumes - XVIII - Monographs (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Miscellaneous Bound Volumes - XIX - Teaching and Research Forum (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - General - Reading File, 1.6
    - Harris, Jane, August-December 1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Harris, Jane, January-February 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Harris, Jane, March-April 1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Harris, Jane, June-September 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Harris, Jane, October-December 1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Harris, Jane, July-September 1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Langham, Max R., January-March 1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Langham, Max R., April-June 1976 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Langham, Max R., July-August 1976 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Langham, Max R., September-December 1976 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Retzlaff, Ralph, August-September 1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Retzlaff, Ralph, October 1975 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Retzlaff, Ralph, November-December 1975 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Retzlaff, Ralph, January 1976 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Retzlaff, Ralph, February-March 1976 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Retzlaff, Ralph, April-June 1976 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Retzlaff, Ralph, August-September 1976 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Retzlaff, Ralph, October-December 1976 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Retzlaff, Ralph, August-September 1977 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Ruttan, Vernon, January-February 1975 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Ruttan, Vernon, March-April 1975 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Ruttan, Vernon, May-June 1975 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Ruttan, Vernon, July-August 1975 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Ruttan, Vernon, September-October 1975 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Ruttan, Vernon, November-December 1975 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Ruttan, Vernon, January-February 1976 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Ruttan, Vernon, March-April 1976 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Ruttan, Vernon, May 1976 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Ruttan, Vernon, June 1976 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Ruttan, Vernon, July-August 1976 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Ruttan, Vernon, September-October 1976 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Ruttan, Vernon, November 1976 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Ruttan, Vernon, December 1976 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Ruttan, Vernon, August 1977 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Stevenson, A. Russell, January-February 1975 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Stevenson, A. Russell, March-April 1975 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Stevenson, A. Russell, June-July 1975 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Stevenson, A. Russell, August-September 1975 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Stevenson, A. Russell, October-December 1975 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Stevenson, A. Russell, January-February 1976 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Stevenson, A. Russell, March-April 1976 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Stevenson, A. Russell, May-June 1976 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Stevenson, A. Russell, July-September 1976 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Stevenson, A. Russell, October-December 1976 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Tongue, Grace, January-April 1975 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Tongue, Grace, May-August 1975 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Tongue, Grace, September-December 1975 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Tongue, Grace, January-February 1976 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Tongue, Grace, March-May 1976 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Tongue, Grace, June-July 1976 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Tongue, Grace, August-September 1976 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Tongue, Grace, October-December 1976 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Weisblat, A.M., December 1974-October 1975 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Weisblat, A.M., November-December 1975 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Weisblat, A.M., January-March 1976 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Weisblat, A.M., April-September 1976 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Weisblat, A.M., October-December 1976 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - New York Office, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - New York Office, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Singapore Office, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Singapore Office, January-March 1976 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Singapore Office, April-November 1976 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Singapore Office, July-August 1977 (Box 9, Folder 63)
- American Universities Research Program, 1956-1970; 2
  Series 2 is arranged in 3 subseries:
  Subseries 1 - General Subseries 2 - Workshops Subseries 3 - Grants
  The American Universities Research Program (AURP), which was in operation from 1963 through 1968, was a program to encourage American professors to study problems in developing countries. This series includes material pertaining to AURP-sponsored workshops and grants.
  - American Universities Research Program - General, 2.1
    - General (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Advisory Committee (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Application (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Budget (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Consultant - Shao-er Ong (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Grant - Macaspac, Travel (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Grant - Registry, 1963-1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Grant - Registry, 1963-1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Grant - Society for International Development, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Grant - Summaries, 1963-1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Grant - Summaries, 1963-1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Grant Committee (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Information (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - List and Forms - Seminar (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Monographs - General (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Monographs - Correspondence - Eicher (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Monographs - Correspondence - Foster (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Monographs - Correspondence - Lombardo (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Monographs - Correspondence - McLoughlin (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Monographs - Correspondence - Taylor (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Preliminary Planning - The Council on Economic and Cultural Affairs, Inc. (CECA)/Ford Foundation Conference (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Preliminary Planning - Blackmore University Visit (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Preliminary Programming (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Program Evaluation, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Progress Reports, 1963-1970 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Progress Reports, 1963-1970 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Regional Conferences, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Research Priorities (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Workshops/Seminars - Expenses (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous Group of Materials, 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - American Universities Research Program - Workshops, 2.2
    - Agricultural Development Research, November 15-16, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Agricultural Development Research, November 15-16, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Geography and Agricultural Development, April 26-28, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Agricultural Market Reform and International Economic Development, May 4-5, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Agricultural Market Reform and International Economic Development, May 4-5, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Role of Agriculture in Economic Development, May 13-16, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Communications in Agricultural Development, October 5-13, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Communications in Agricultural Development, October 5-13, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Market Patterns and Problems at Early Stages of Commercialization of Agriculture, October 19-21, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Market Patterns and Problems at Early Stages of Commercialization of Agriculture, October 19-21, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Role of Cooperatives and Other Volunteer Organizations in Agricultural Development, October 22-24, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Role of Cooperatives and Other Volunteer Organizations in Agricultural Development, October 22-24, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Geography and Agricultural Development, November 20-21, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Geography and Agricultural Development, November 20-21, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Intersectoral Relations in Economic Development, November 20-21, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Intersectoral Relations in Economic Development, November 20-21, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Historical Studies of the Development of Marketing Institutions, November 22-24, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Content of Education for Accelerated Agricultural Development, January 29-31, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Marketing, March 1-3, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Restructuring Agricultural Curricula in Southeast Asia Universities, March 7-8, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Agriculture and Economic Development, May 2-4, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Administrative and Political Factors in Land Reform in Asia, May 14-15, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Planning of Agricultural Development, May 20-22, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Planning of Agricultural Development, May 20-22, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Labor Surplus and Dual Economy Models, May 29-30, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Functions, Forms and Objectives of Agricultural Extension and Community Development, June 4-6, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Functions, Forms and Objectives of Agricultural Extension and Community Development, June 4-6, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Re-examination of Farm Management for Serving Farmers in Technically Less Advanced Countries, June 24-25, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Re-examination of Farm Management for Serving Farmers in Technically Less Advanced Countries, June 24-25, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Role of Transportation in Agricultural Development, September 12-14, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Role of Transportation in Agricultural Development, September 12-14, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Influence of Primary Export Trade Patterns upon the Agricultural Development of Developing Nations, September 24-26, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Role of Aerial Studies in Agricultural Development, October 24-26, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Role of Aerial Studies in Agricultural Development, October 24-26, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Institutional Structures and Cultural Values as Related to Agricultural Development, October 28-30, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Institutional Structures and Cultural Values as Related to Agricultural Development, October 28-30, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Influence of Primary Exports Upon Agricultural Development, November 20-21, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Techniques for Evaluating Rural Village Development Projects, December 7, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Techniques for Evaluating Rural Village Development Projects, December 7, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Farm Management Research in Developing Areas, January 12-13, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Farm Management Research in Developing Areas, January/March 1966 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Farm Management Research in Developing Areas, January/March 1966 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Problems of Land Settlement and Development in the Tropics, February 11-13, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Problems of Land Settlement and Development in the Tropics, February 11-13, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Implications for Research in Comparative Administration for the Conduct of Programs in Agricultural Development, February 14-15, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Implications for Research in Comparative Administration for the Conduct of Programs in Agricultural Development, February 14-15, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Supply and Market Surplus Relationships in Peasant Agriculture, February 18-20, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Industrialization and Agricultural Development, February 25-26, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Research Implications of Recent Developments in International Agricultural Policies and Arrangements, March 11-13, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Research Implications of Recent Developments in International Agricultural Policies and Arrangements, March 11-13, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Purchased Inputs, Mechanization and Water Use, March 14-15, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Purchased Inputs, Mechanization and Water Use, March 14-15, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Purchased Inputs, Mechanization and Water Use, March 14-15, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Farm Management Research in Developing Areas, March 31-April 2, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Economic Aspects of the Operation and Development of Irrigation Districts, April 22-24, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Economic Aspects of the Operation and Development of Irrigation Districts, April 22-24, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Planning Agricultural Development, June 3-5, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Planning Agricultural Development, June 3-5, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Social and Political Movements of Rural Peoples in Relation to Agricultural Development, October 20-22, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Social and Political Movements of Rural Peoples in Relation to Agricultural Development, October 20-22, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Data Requirements for Agriculture Development in East Africa, November 10-12, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Data Requirements for Agriculture Development in East Africa, November 10-12, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Adapting Cooperatives and Quasi-Cooperatives to the Market Structures and Conditions of Underdeveloped Areas, April 26-30, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Adapting Cooperatives and Quasi-Cooperatives to the Market Structures and Conditions of Underdeveloped Areas, April 26-30, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Adapting Cooperatives and Quasi-Cooperatives to the Market Structures and Conditions of Underdeveloped Areas, April 26-30, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Adapting Cooperatives and Quasi-Cooperatives to the Market Structures and Conditions of Underdeveloped Areas, April 26-30, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Adapting Cooperatives and Quasi-Cooperatives to the Market Structures and Conditions of Underdeveloped Areas, April 26-30, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Agricultural Development Seminar, April 29-30, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Agricultural Development Seminar, April 29-30, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Agricultural Development Seminar, April 29-30, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Agricultural Development Seminar, April 29-30, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - Agricultural Development Seminar, April 29-30, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Agricultural Development Seminar, April 29-30, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Latin American Agricultural Development, July 25-27, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 74)
      Related Materials
    - Latin American Agricultural Development, July 25-27, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - Latin American Agricultural Development, July 25-27, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - Latin American Agricultural Development, July 25-27, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - Latin American Agricultural Development, July 25-27, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - Training for International Rural Sociologists, September 25-26/November 27-28, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 79)
    - Training for International Rural Sociologists, September 25-26/November 27-28, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 80)
    - Core Economics, October 10-11, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 81)
    - Core Economics, October 10-11, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 82)
    - Core Economics, October 10-11, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 83)
    - Core Economics, October 10-11, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 84)
    - Core Economics, October 10-11, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 85)
    - Competing Demands for the Time of Labor in Traditional African Societies, October 19-21, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 86)
    - Competing Demands for the Time of Labor in Traditional African Societies, October 19-21, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 87)
    - Competing Demands for the Time of Labor in Traditional African Societies, October 19-21, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 88)
    - Problems of Teaching and Research in Farm Management with Special Reference to Developing Areas, January 16-18, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 89)
    - Problems of Teaching and Research in Farm Management with Special Reference to Developing Areas, January 16-18, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 90)
    - Problems of Teaching and Research in Farm Management with Special Reference to Developing Areas, January 16-18, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 91)
    - Problems of Teaching and Research in Farm Management with Special Reference to Developing Areas, January 16-18, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 92)
    - A Systems Analysis of Improved Food Consumption and Crop Allocation, March 8-10, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 93)
    - Peasant Motivation and Economic Behavior, April 23-24, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 94)
    - Peasant Motivation and Economic Behavior, April 23-24, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 95)
    - Research on Economics of Agricultural Development in East and West Africa, June 9-14, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 96)
    - Research on Economics of Agricultural Development in East and West Africa, June 9-14, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 97)
    - Research on Economics of Agricultural Development in East and West Africa, June 9-14, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 98)